question_data = [
    {'category': "General Knowledge", 'type': "boolean", 'difficulty': "easy",
     'question': "French is an official language in Canada.", 'correct_answer': "True",
     'incorrect_answers': ["False"]},
    {'category': "General Knowledge", 'type': "boolean", 'difficulty': "easy",
                                       'question': "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
                                       'correct_answer': "False", 'incorrect_answers': ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Pluto is a planet.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
